Uh that's what I play. Uh wasn't feel
嗯，我玩的就是这个。 呃，感觉状态不是
100%. But you know it's been a busy
百分之百。 但你知道，
schedule for the team and T has been out
球队最近日程很忙，T
today. So I just want to be with them
今天缺席了。 所以，我只想和他们
over there, you know, and help help the
在一起，你知道，帮助
team and do as I can do on the court,
球队，在球场上尽我所能
you know. Uh well, it didn't work. I
。 呃，结果失败了。
just got to, you know, be get better and
你知道，我得让自己变得更好，
for my body and on the court, you know,
为了我的身体，也为了在球场上的表现，你知道，
and we're just going to turn the Jews
我们要让犹太人兴奋起来
on. And so I win.
。 所以，我赢了。   在
And before I know you kind of been
我了解你作为替补球员
watching from a different perspective
从不同角度观察
being on the bench, what are you seeing
比赛之前，你对进攻端有什么看法？
clicking for you guys recently?
最近你们觉得哪些方面没有奏效？
&gt;&gt; I mean, we just got to be more
我的意思是，我们必须更积极
aggressive, you know, uh, we got to look
主动一些，你知道，呃，我们必须盯紧
at the rim. Uh, shots is not falling.
篮筐。 呃，子弹没落下来。
So, we just got to get the offensive
所以，我们只需要抢到进攻
rebounds. We got to play hard, you know.
篮板就行了。 我们必须全力以赴，你知道的。
Shots not going to fall in all the time.
球不可能每次都进。
We're going to miss. It's going to have
我们会想念你的。 情况会急转直下
a bad times, bad uh, turn, bad turn two.
，非常糟糕，呃，糟糕，第二次急转直下。
So, you know, been playing a lot of road
你知道，最近打了很多客场
games lately and that's make you a
比赛，这让你在
little bit um tired mentally, too. You
精神上也有些疲惫。 你
know what I'm saying? So, I'm glad we're
明白我的意思吗？ 所以，我很高兴我们
going back home now and we have some
现在要回家了，我们在
couple games out there. Hopefully, we
那里还有几场比赛。 希望我们
can play like how we used to play.
能像以前那样打球。
&gt;&gt; Given how well you guys play at home,
鉴于你们主场战绩如此出色，在经历了这么
bank some wins after so many road games?
多客场比赛之后，你们有多期待接下来的主场比赛，希望能借此机会赢下几场胜利？   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。
&gt;&gt; Uh I'm looking forward to win. you know,
嗯，我期待着胜利。 你知道，
we're going to actually, you know, is
我们其实要找个借口，那就是
excuse we're playing outside a lot of
我们经常在场外打
games, but uh we just got to start
比赛，但是，我们必须开始
winning. Uh when we go home, I think
赢球了。 嗯，我觉得回家也会
it's going to help a little bit too, you
有点帮助，你
know, um seeing family, spend some time
知道，嗯，见到家人，和家人待一段时间
family, uh and just safe to home,
，嗯，回家很安全，
protect home.
保护好家。
&gt;&gt; And when guys just aren't seeing jumpers
当球员们看不到自己投篮命中时
falling, do you think that affects some
，你认为这是否会影响
of the stuff you were talking about like
你刚才提到的一些方面，比如
aggression, wanting to attack offensive
侵略性，以及在
when you aren't seeing your shots
看不到自己
falling that you're used to seeing? Um I
习惯的投篮命中率时，是否还想积极进攻？ 嗯，我
don't think it affect maybe it affects
不认为这会直接影响到我们，也许只会影响
by individually you know even affects me
到我个人，你知道，甚至我
too when I miss the my shots it affects
自己投篮不中也会受到影响，
me so I'm sure it's just like it doesn't
所以我相信这不会直接
affect the team I mean affects the team
影响到球队。我的意思是，对球队的影响可能不大，
a little bit you know we got to wide
你知道，我们有很多空位
open shots and can make it it's when
投篮的机会，而且我们都能投进，但当
somebody gets down is affects a lot of
有人投篮不中时，也会影响到很多
people too so you know we just got to be
人。所以，我们需要
got more professional and even if if we
更加职业，即使投篮不
miss we got to play solid defense and
中，我们也必须打出稳固的防守，并且
cross the board position
做好场上每个位置的准备。
Where did this game get away from you
这场比赛你们是怎么输的
guys? Because it was a it was a 13-point
？ 因为虽然比分是13分
game, but it wasn't really a 13-point
，但实际上并不是13分之差
game. It was a two-point game with four
。 比赛还剩四分钟时，比分只差两分，然后就突然
know, fell apart.
崩盘了。
&gt;&gt; Best um being is a good good team, you
最好的情况就是组建一支优秀的团队，你
know. Uh we never lost this year like
知道的。 呃，我们今年从来没有输过那种
bad games like that. So we always it's
糟糕的比赛。 所以我们总是打得很
always close games because we are a good
胶着，因为我们是一支优秀的
team. We never give up, you know.
球队。 你知道，我们从不放弃。